Hello
everyone, welcome to my new video.
Today, I will be talking about the new updates of the very popular plan called Elevate by ICICI Lampard. Today, I will be talking about the new updates of the very popular plan called Elevate by
ICICI Lampard. A customer who wants to take a health insurance policy should be very careful in choosing the company. Its benefits, the company's claim settlement ratio, the sales service, these are the main factors. Considering all these, ICICI Lampard's Elevate plan can
definitely be chosen.
Some good changes that have come recently have made this
plan more attractive and popular.
This plan has become a huge scheme that is 100 percent fair to the money spent by the customers. If
we take a health insurance policy and want to
get a claim for a patient,
24 hours of
hospitalization was mandatory earlier,
but with the advent of this update,
only two hours of hospitalization is required in this Elevate plan.
And secondly, we can
say that
this is the most important thing.  There is a benefit called unlimited registration,
that is, in the policies, we
take an insurance policy, for example, if we take a sum of Rs.
10 lakhs, we have taken a sum of Rs.
10 lakhs, and once the patient is hospitalized, the bill is paid in full
or the payment is
made to the hospital, and the
actual balance is zero, there is no sum of Rs. 10 lakhs that year, but
after 45 days, we restore another Rs. 10
lakhs and register the sum of Rs. 10 lakhs to the patient.
It is called unlimited registration. It will
restore this sum of Rs. 10 lakhs for as long as it takes. But in the
previous Elevate plan, there
was a gap period of 45 days, but now if we
say that the gap period has been taken, even if we
buy a claim of Rs. 10 lakhs and it is in the
sum of Rs. 10 lakhs,
the customer gets the benefit of that sum of Rs. 10 lakhs immediately. The
third
important point is that
it is only for NRIs, that is  It is
only for expatriates. When
taking a policy for expatriates, they will be given a 25%
NRI discount. This is an
important change. In
my opinion,
all expatriates should
see this as a golden opportunity and
take the Elevate plan of ICISA today. One of the
conditions in this is that the expatriate must be a member of the
insurance policy he is taking. In that
insurance
policy, he, his wife and
children must be included
or he must be
included in the insurance policy.
That is another condition. In addition, those with a CIBIL score of
750 or more will be given a
15% discount on the premium as a CIBIL discount. If you
add the add-on called Jump Start, the
waiting period for ABCD, which used to be two or three years for asthma, blood pressure, cholesterol, diabetes, and EAS diseases will be reduced to just one
month. It is
called Specific Illness for about 21 diseases, which are our
cataracts, piles, varicose veins,
such a 21  Diseases Before these diseases, there is a
two-year waiting period in
all companies. All health
insurance companies have a two-year
mandatory waiting period,
but in our new update, there is an add-on to reduce this
waiting period to one year. The
upper age limit for taking this policy is 125 years. No
other company
gives insurance policies up to this age of 125.
That too without any copayment or condition.
This policy is given up to the age of 125. If we
say this copayment, we must have taken a policy suppository and
said in it that if it says 20% or 30%
copayment, then after a claim
comes, only after 20% or 30% of that
customer is paid in the hospital, the
remaining amount is
given to the company. That is the copayment. But in
this policy, the policy is issued up to the age of 125 without any copayment.
With all these benefits,
ICICI  We can assume that the Elevate plan with Lombard's new updates is
better than any other health policy plan.
Of course, we can
take it boldly and recommend it. In
this, the
three main elements that I mentioned earlier,
after-sales service,
claim settlement ratio, and
benefits, are the
three elements that we should pay attention to when taking a policy. The
current structure of this plan is 100 percent fair. When we
say claim settlement,
you
can see that the
claim settlement ratio of ICC Lombard is 99.7% free. We can
confidently take
this policy with the assurance that we will get the claim. When we
say after-sales service, the
after-sales service of ICICI Lombard is very good,
you will experience it.
Benefits: I have already said that
this policy has very excellent, excellent, beautiful benefits.
We can confidently recommend it to anyone
today.  Get ICICI
Lampard's Elevate Health Plan and
secure your life.